Fellow citizens,
in obedience to the will of the people,
and in their presence by the authority
vested in me by this oath I assume
the arduous and responsible duties
of President of the United States.
Relying upon the support of my countrymen,
and invoking the guidance of Almighty God,
our faith teaches that there is no safer
reliance than upon the God
of our fathers who has
so singularly favored the American
people in every national trial
and who will not forsake us
so long as we obey his commandments
and walk humbly in his footsteps the respo
nsibilities of the high trust to which I
have been called always of grave importanc
e are augmented by the prevailing business
conditions entailing idleness upon willing
labor and loss to useful enterprises.
The country is suffering from industrial
disturbances from which speedy relief must
be had our financial
system needs some revision.
Our money is all good now, but its
value must not further be threatened.